[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
Say your prayers
because you're about to die.
[Damian] I'm sorry.
I didn't want to do this.
[Raul] Let Diego go!
He has nothing to do with this!
-[gunshots]
-[groans]
Dad? You're the Jaguar?
[Raul] I only wear that mask
to guarantee your safety,
to keep you from danger.
To keep you safe from Red Dragon.
[Diego] This is the key
to Red Dragon's world.
[Lily] I'll catch you, Mercedes Palacio.
-Are you okay?
-I'm sorry. Yes.
[man] The keycard. I think I lost it.
Mercedes, I can't reach you
on your cellphone.
I've been trying to call you.
You need to report to me, ASAP.
[Lily] Helena Montoya as Red Dragon.
And now, my enemy finally has a face.
[Emilia] I'm sure whoever
was on the other line
plans to take you down.
[Helena] Anyone that battles a dragon
should be ready to die in a blaze.
[Lily] I need stronger evidence.
Then she'll go to prison
and pay for what she did to Aguas Realty.
-[Diego] I've got an idea.
-[Lily] I trust you.
[Diego] I can infiltrate
Red Dragon's hideout.
[Emilia] I'm sure, you'll have
even more fun now
because Emilia Ardiente Torillo is here,
the only daughter of Helena Montoya.
[Lily] I can't go on with this project
if your daughter, Emilia, meddles in.
-Helena!
-[metal clanks]
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Are you sure? You might have an injury.
Mama! Move it!
Stay away! Mama.
-Lily.
-Mama.
-Mama, are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-Were you hurt?
-Lily dear, are you hurt?
-No, I'm fine.
Lily, don't ever do that again, okay?
-I'm sorry.
-Come here.
[pensive music playing]
-Jepoy.
-Yes?
What did you mean when you said
Lily needed an ally?
Do you know someone
who wants to help Lily?
I do.
Who?
I want to help Lily.
In her fight against the Ardientes.
It's going to be a tactical alliance.
It should've been like
that a long time ago
since we have the same enemies.
Someone does want to help Lily.
But you wouldn't like it
if I told you who,
so… never mind.
Who is it?
-Do you really want to know?
-Why can't you say it?
It's Natalie.
Natalie? Are you serious, Jepoy?
You actually trust that woman?
And you plan on telling Lily that?
I don't get it, Anna.
You're so convinced that someone
like Arnaldo can change.
But now that Natalie wants to
help us, you think it's wrong.
I don't get you either.
You've seen that Arnaldo has changed,
but you can't accept it.
I don't buy it.
But it's so easy for you to trust Natalie!
Probably 'cause you aren't
thinking with your head.
[tense music playing]
[pensive music playing]
Sir.
Should I go fetch Madam Helena?
[thud]
Helena Montoya…
is a bloodsucking leech!
To think…
to think that… that woman,
that red-faced woman
would have the decency
to face me!
[scoffs]
She's not going to come back here.
And if she does, I'm sure that…
it's for one thing, and one thing alone.
She'd like to swallow me whole
and chew me into little pieces
and spit me out like
an overused chewing gum.
[exhales sharply]
Helena… Helena…
The only woman…
who can make my blood curdle
and make me look stupid!
This should not, this will not,
this must not happen again!
[thuds]
Relax, Julio. Relax.
She's not worth getting all worked up for.
Relax. [exhales]
Relax.
Damn you, Helena!
[slow tense music playing]
What was that all about?
Natalie just wanted to help
but she went and got all mad like that.
Wha--What's her problem?
[phone ringing]
She's getting me in trouble with Anna.
[phone continues ringing]
Ma'am, where are you? We need to talk.
Mom, just wait for me here.
I'll just go check on the dragon
and her daughter.
Lily…
Mom, let me do this.
I'll just give them
a taste of what's to come.
I'll be right back.
Helena?
-Lily.
-How are you? Doc, how is she?
Should I take her to the hospital?
-No need.
-Or anything?
-Lily.
-Are you sure?
Who died and made you daughter
of the year?
Stop acting like you're close to my mama!
It's over the top!
Emilia, stop it. Please.
You know what, Emilia?
You're very lucky that
you reunited with your mother.
And about what I did earlier,
I want you to know
that I didn't regret saving her.
Shouldn't you be thanking me, instead?
Oh, knock it off!
[sighs] As usual…
Good thing you're my friend, Helena.
Anyway, can I ask you a favor?
Yeah. Sure.
What is it?
Like I said before,
I feel at ease with you.
I want you to know that anytime,
you can call me.
Remember what I told you
when we had lunch?
You're like the glamorous mother
I never had.
Remember?
So…
if it's all right with you
and you don't mind…
I want to call you Mama.
You think it's okay?
But, of course!
You can call me Mama. Baby girl.
[chuckles]
Thank you! Thank you, Mama.
You're…
[tense music playing]
I'm so happy that you're
calling me baby girl!
You're so sweet, Helena. I mean, Mama.
You're so sweet!
And so are you.
[tense music swells]
That's enough!
Mama, let's go.
-You're okay now, right?
-Yeah.
Remember, Mama, you can call me anytime.
Yes, I will.
Mercedes, gather our best men.
The arms shipment
with Mr. Yi will push through.
All right. Bye.
Is everything good?
That's great to hear.
Oh! Baby girl!
-Oh, Mama!
-What are you still doing here?
Oh, I didn't see you there. Um…
Let's go home together.
You know… I still don't know
how I can thank you enough
for saving my life.
[clicks tongue] Mama…
It was just a coincidence
that I was there.
Anyone would've saved you.
Honestly, I can sense that you
are a very good person.
You continue to amaze me every day!
How can I ever repay you, Lily?
A hug?
-Sure.
-Mama.
[tense music playing]
Thank you, Doctor.
And you!
This is your daughter's fault!
If she hadn't left,
Mama wouldn't have followed her.
Look what almost happened!
Say whatever you want to, Emilia,
but that's not how I see it.
Oh really?
Aren't you jealous, Camia?
Your daughter's already
cozying up to my mother.
You heard her. She calls my mom "Mama."
Doesn't it make you wonder
if she would risk her life for you too?
Nothing really beats
your desperation, Emilia.
You're even taking
your insecurities out on me.
And to answer your question: Yes.
My daughter would risk her life for me.
She lived as Ivy Aguas.
She was buried alive
and came back as Lily Cruz.
What about you, Emilia?
Can you sacrifice to that extent
for your own mother?
[tense music playing]
I did what you wanted me to do. That's it.
I can't join your operations.
I need to focus on my group.
That'd be fine if you
accomplished your mission.
But Diego Torillo is still alive!
Quite forgetful, aren't we?
I kept telling you
that Diego Torillo escaped.
We looked for him
everywhere too, but he's gone.
So, you admit you're a failure?
[guns click]
Keep this in mind, Jaguar:
If you don't show up
to the operation later,
this bullet will lodge itself
in the head of your beloved Camia.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Helena] Mercedes, gather our best men.
The arms shipment with Mr. Yi
will push through.
Lily?
Diego?
It's confirmed.
Red Dragon is making a shipment tonight.
Where are you?
Give me the address.
I'll sabotage their delivery.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Lily] This will all come
to an end, Diego.
We'll be free from all this
and live in peace.
But for now,
we've got a fight on our hands.
[Diego] Forgive me, Dad.
But I have to do this.
Lily.
Mom, try not to worry.
Diego said he'll help carry out
all of my plans.
Lily, I know just how hard and
dangerous this fight of ours is.
But I also know how brave,
skilled, and intelligent you are.
I know you can handle yourself.
[soft piano music playing]
On my end,
I know that no matter how much
you support me in my battles,
you still worry so much about me.
We almost lost each other
so many times before.
[soft piano music continues playing]
Mom, I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Mom.
Hold on, Lily.
You don't have to apologize
to me about anything.
We both chose to do what's right,
no matter how hard it is.
No matter how many dragons
or demons we have to face,
always remember
that I will be right beside you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Why are you so quiet, Emilia?
Baby girl, baby girl,
baby girl. Baby girl?
[exhales sharply] Emilia…
I do not have time
for your issues right now.
[Diego] Diego, you
can't let them catch you.
You have to find out where
they're keeping their guns.
Jan, you may leave.
Excuse me, Madam.
Jaguar has arrived.
The operation will now commence.
Excellent.
Wow, because of that,
you can live another day.
Excuse me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshots]
[Damian] You're here again, Fake Jaguar?!
[Camia] If you stay here,
you can protect Lily
and Lily can protect you,
especially since you've already
left Red Dragon's syndicate.
Damian, don't forget we all love you.
We're ready to fight with you,
as long as you stay true to us.
[Damian] You can get out of this, Damian.
No one knows what happened. No one.
[tense music playing]
[exhales sharply]
And this is how Helena Montoya
becomes Red Dragon.
Is that the reason why you
changed your outfit to red,
-Mama?
-Yes.
Stunning!
The wealth that sustains us,
is the death of others.
Are you listening to me, dear daughter?
Dear daughter? Is that me, Mama?
I'm getting confused
because you allowed Lily Cruz
to call you "Mama."
[sighs] So, we're actually
having this talk.
Are you really jealous of Lily Cruz?
Is it my fault?
Did I not brief you on our plan of action?
I know, Mama. You're just
luring her to your spider web.
But you know, I can't help but notice.
Something is different.
It seems different to me.
It's not just an act of kindness
that you see in Lily Cruz.
Something's different.
Hmm… But I'm warning you, Mama,
don't be fooled by her M.O.
I should know because I fell
into her trap back then.
You know what she did to me before, Mama?
She got close to me
and she almost took a bullet for my life.
She saved my life. Exactly the same thing
that she's doing to you right now, Mama.
She saved your life, right?
See what kind of person
our little "friend" is?
[tense music playing]
Mom, I think I need to help Diego.
But you can't go into Helena's hideout.
She can't find out that you know
she's Red Dragon.
Hi, Jaguar.
There's something
different about you tonight.
Do you know how long
I've wanted to do this?
[groans]
Mom, I have to find a way
to help Diego's plan succeed.
I'm sorry.
[phone ringing]
Speak of the devil.
No, Mama. Don't! Don't.
If what you say is true,
I need to keep her close
to see that chameleon's true colors.
[phone continues ringing]
Hello, Lily.
This is what I like about you.
You don't give in so easily.
[groans, grunts]
Hold him steady!
Aren't you tired of fantasizing
over that overgrown cat?!
Enough!
Get a move on, Jaguar!
Mr. Yi is waiting.
[soft music playing]
Anna?
Is something wrong? You look restless.
[Natalie] What?!
You mean to say
that Lily Cruz refused my help?
Is she insane?
I don't think she would do such a thing.
She knows very well
that I have a lot of money
and I have an army.
I could probably be her best ally!
So, Madrigal,
why don't you tell me the truth?
Who doesn't want me
to join forces with Lily Cruz?
Hmm?
It's Anna.
[scoffs] What?
How can I know if what
I'm feeling is really love
and not just something else?
Well…
Love does not delight in evil,
but rejoices in truth.
It always protects, always trusts,
always hopes, always perseveres.
Love never fails.
This is bad.
Then it really is love.
[scoffs]
You mean to tell me
that this simple-minded,
conniving little witch,
who is a barrio girl, by the way,
is sabotaging our plans?
Natalie, don't think of her that way.
We're just friends.
So, you're siding with your friend?
Is that what you're telling me?
I'm getting tired of you listening to her.
It's not funny.
If you're not going to help me,
just leave.
I don't need your help.
I can handle myself.
And just so you know, Madrigal…
No matter what you do, you can't stop me.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Lily.
-Mama.
What's the emergency?
Nothing. Um. After what happened earlier,
I just thought you might want to relax.
So…
For you, Mama. It's on me.
You look stressed, Mama.
How important is that…
shipment of yours?
How did you know about that?
Well…
During the medical mission,
I kind of overheard you on the phone.
Oh… that. [chuckles]
Um,
I'm still fixing
a few things here and there.
But you're right. I do need a drink.
Is this poisoned?
I'm not like that.
[suspenseful music playing]
Cheers.
You know the drill.
Are we doing this all night?
Jaguar, open the vault now!
[suspenseful music playing]
[both laugh]
So, Mama,
who among your clients
is giving you a headache?
Well, let's see…
There's this one. He's too specific.
He wants to make sure that all
the pieces work in precision.
He wants to strike everyone
who sees the product.
[laughs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[buttons beeping]
Strike everyone?
Yes! Like a gunshot through the heart!
Otherwise, why would I do all of this
if it's not going to help
fund my projects, right?
Including my creations.
My products are meant
to strike any target.
[beeps]
Want a sample?
Bang!
[alarm blares]
[both laugh]
[alarm blaring]
[gunshot]
This is none of your business.
You really are like the Madam.
You people work too fast.
I changed the vault's passcode last night.
[tense music playing]
[alarm blares]
That's the problem with you,
Mercedes, you need to chill.
Go ahead, Jaguar. Load it up.
Boys.
[tense music playing]
Damian…
Damian!
What secret is Helena Montoya hiding?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know there's something
you're not telling me.
And I know you didn't come
with me and Lily back then
because you're avoiding her.
I got sick, remember?
Damian…
I don't want Lily to get hurt.
So tell me if I should be worried!
My daughter's going to meet
with Helena Montoya.
Is she safe, Damian?
Answer me!
I don't know Helena Montoya.
I know what you mean, Ma--
Helena.
Yes, that's right.
And you know what? I…
I really have always sensed
a connection between us.
Oh, and speaking of shipment,
I just have to make
one quick phone call, okay?
-I'll be right back.
-Okay.
[phone vibrates]
We're moving the shipment to the truck.
You know what to do.
Yes.
Mercedes, how's everything?
Perfect. There's just one hiccup.
What?
Don't worry, Madam.
Jaguar will deliver the shipment on time.
Excellent.
Be careful.
I will.
[suspenseful music playing]
So…
Where were we?
Sit down.
I'm sorry. I have a lot
of transactions myself.
I know we're both busy people.
But, you see? I make time for you.
Should I be grateful?
You should.
[Julio] Helena, I love you.
Once I achieve my dream
of becoming president,
you'll be my first lady.
[Helena] Of course, Julio.
I love you.
I love you too, Helena.
You whore! You lied to me!
Damn!
-Hello, ex-lover.
-Helena. You came back.
I'm back. Well and alive.
[Julio] So you want to play games, Helena?
Fine. I'll join in on the fun.
After all, I know just how much
of a sore loser you can be.
And I can't wait to see
that look on your face again.
[Anna] How can I know if what
I'm feeling is really love?
Love does not delight in evil,
but rejoices in truth.
It always protects,
always trusts, always hopes,
always perseveres.
Love never fails.
[Anna] Cut it out, Anna.
Just forget about your feelings.
You're only going to get yourself hurt.
Just accept the fact
that Jepoy likes someone else.
It's not your fault he likes airheads.
They deserve one another.
Anna, wait!
[dramatic music playing]
It's been 35 days.
Hasn't that been long enough, Attorney?
I thought you were expediting
my suspension.
I did, Julio. But that's not the problem.
But the charges of frustrated homicide
that Camia Cruz pressed
against you are still in effect.
So you're telling me that we
can work around my suspension,
but that I still can't become
governor because of Camia Cruz?
-Exactly.
-[scoffs]
Colonel.
Find out who all those witnesses were
on the day I shot Camia Cruz.
Let them know that they fired first,
and that's why we fired back!
Yes, sir.
What do you plan to do next?
I am going to solve a simple problem
with an age-old solution
so that I can get my position
as governor back,
and rule this province once again.
So please, Attorney, please…
just attend to all these legalities
and whatever else needs to be done
so we can get all this nonsense over with.
-Right away, sir.
-Yes, please.
[exhales sharply]
-Oh, Emilia.
-Papa.
Where is your mother?
I thought she was dropping by for dinner.
She's having drinks with Lily Cruz.
[scoffs]
She stood us up for--
You know what? This is all your fault.
See? Even your own mother
doesn't want to be with you!
[laughing]
Mama has a plan.
So, if you want to pursue her,
go to her directly, not through me.
Besides, I'm not
your stupid cupid, you know?
I'm not expecting this family
to ever become whole again
because Mama doesn't need you,
and neither do I.
We both don't need you!
You are getting too big
for your breeches, Emilia.
What are you so smug about, huh?
Your mother?
Well, I've got news for you.
Just because I'm not governor right now,
doesn't mean you can treat me
like an old rag!
Very soon, I am going to get
my governorship back.
Sooner than you think!
You and your mother will have to
take a backseat in this family.
The two of you will pay
for all the disgrace
and humiliation you've given me.
[screams]
[scoffs]
You spoiled little brat.
[tense music playing]
Come back with the money
at exactly 10:00 p.m.
Make sure it's the exact amount.
I'll go with you.
I can manage.
You don't know where to deliver the goods.
Just leave it to me.
If you really know, tell us.
That's not necessary.
You know what to do with him.
[suspenseful music playing]
[groans, grunts]
Don't let him escape!
Well, Lily, I think it's time
for me to go.
I'm not a young 'un anymore.
I can't stay up late.
Besides, I must oversee the shipment.
[phone rings]
Oh, here's an update.
[phone continues ringing]
What is the meaning of this?
Didn't we say… no phones?
We said no such things.
[tense music playing]
Come on, Helena.
[grunts]
You can ignore your own daughter,
but not me.
Not me.
More than a thousand firearms
amounting to 50 million pesos
are currently in police custody
after being seized
from a shipment made by Red Dragon.
The fight continues, Mom.
Am I going to have someone buried soon?
Yes.
I'm done playing games with Red Dragon.
I've lost my patience.
[Julio] Julio Ardiente is still
king of the province of Ardiente.
Diego's pretending to be Jaguar.
[Diego] As long as I'm alive,
you'll never be the governor
of this province.
[theme music playing]